ithinkimlost.com 2015-12-31

# ITIL JET Programme / Japan Forum

## Privacy Policy

IThinkImLost (hereafter referred to as ITIL) has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of the users of our websites. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users.

## What this Privacy Statement Covers

  * This privacy statement covers ITIL's treatment of personally identifiable information collected by ITIL through a website owned and operated by ITIL.
  * This privacy statement does not apply to the practices of companies that ITIL does not own or control, or of persons that ITIL does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which ITIL's websites link.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

  * You can visit the websites of ITIL without revealing any personal information. However, ITIL needs certain personal information if you wish to register for a members account, receive a ITIL newsletter, or use certain ITIL services.
  * Where required, this information may include your personal contact information. ITIL will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to set up your members account, to provide you with requested services, and to contact you regarding new services.
  * By accessing the services of ITIL and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy statement.

**Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information**

  * ITIL automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. ITIL may use this information to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfil your requests for certain products and services. However, ITIL does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you.
  * ITIL uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en-GB).

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * ITIL may disclose your personal information when: 
    * We have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose;
    * We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process;
    * We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property of ITIL; or
    * We find that your actions on our websites violate the ITIL Terms of Use document or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

**Consent**

  * If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this statement, please do not provide any personal information to ITIL. If you have provided personal information to ITIL and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify ITIL at [webmaster@ithinkimlost.com](mailto:webmaster@ithinkimlost.com)

**How to Access your Personal Information**

  * ITIL gives you the ability to edit your ITIL Account Information and preferences at any time.

**Third Party Cookies**

  * Notwithstanding anything else in this policy, we or a data provider we have engaged may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data that you have voluntarily submitted to us, or posted to our Web Site. We may share such data with a data provider solely in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these cookies please go to [Ad Choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).
  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.
  * Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [ads preference manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

**Security**

  * Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, your ITIL Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, ITIL uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.
  * We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures.
  * Further, ITIL retains your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes identified above or as required by law.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

  * ITIL may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this statement from time to time. Please review this statement periodically. Your continued use of ITIL websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

**Questions or Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy statement, or your own personal information, please e-mail us at [webmaster@ithinkimlost.com](mailto:webmaster@ithinkimlost.com).

**Opting Out of Third-Party Ad Servers**

* If you want to prevent a third-party ad server from sending and reading cookies on your computer, currently you must visit each ad network's Web site individually and opt out (if they offer this capability).
* If you want to prevent a third-party ad server from sending and reading cookies on your computer, we recommend you block cookies using your browser privacy setting.
